(Penny:)Look, I'm sorry.
(Penny:)I was drunk, I was lonely, I hated Zack.
(Penny:)Can we just forget it ever happened?
(Leonard:)No, it's pretty well imprinted on my brain.
(Leonard:)Especially the whole rodeo thing.
(Penny:)Oh, God.
(Leonard:)So that's it?
Wham, bam, thank you, Leonard?
PENNY: Look, I said I'm sorry.
Can't you please let it go?
(Leonard:)How am I supposed to let it go?
You used me for sex.
(Leonard:)Morning, Mrs. Gunderson.
(Sheldon:)Good morning, Leonard.
Or should I say "yeehaw"?
(Raj:)-Holy crap.
-What?
(Raj:)We finally have proof...
(Raj:)-...that aliens walk among us.
-Excuse me?
(Raj:)The dating site
matched a woman with Sheldon.
(Howard:)You're kidding. An actual woman?
(Raj:)Yeah, look. Breasts and everything.
(Howard:)Trust me, breasts doesn't
necessarily mean "woman."